nextround.net 2014-05-23

# NextRound.net | Level Off From Your Day Job

Maske and Booth created Nextround.net groups and content (herein, “NR”) with the intention of making it easy to share information with your friends, family and extended networks. We give you control of your information because we understand that you may not want to give the world access to the information you share on NR. Our privacy settings allow you to limit the information displayed about you to your group members.

We abide by two main beliefs when it comes to your privacy: (1) You should have control over your personal information. NR helps you share information with your friends, family and extended networks. You choose what information that you want others on the site to see, including personal information, pictures, etc. (2) You should have access to the information others want to share. Sharing information between group members is an essential part of fun interaction. We want to help you easily get that information in order to make interacting with your group members stress free.

**Personal Information (PI) Collection**

We collect personal information when you register with NR, when you use NR groups; when you visit NR groups or when you enter contests, promotions or sweepstakes. We may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register with NR, you have the ability to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address and any other personal or preference information that you opt to provide to us.

We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP addresses NR cookie information, and the page you request.

Information collected by NR when you participate in a contest, promotion or sweepstakes may include your full name, e-mail address, and street address.

When you use NR, you may specify group dynamics, set reminders, create votes, post messages, modify images, create agendas, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you posted or easily view photos you’ve uploaded. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.

**Age limitations**

The Service is not designed for or directed to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 13.

**How Your Personal Information Is Used**

We take appropriate physical and electronic measures to protect against unauthorized access to, alteration of, and disclosure of Personal Information.

We use the information we collect for the following purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see; fulfill requests for products and service; improve our Service; contact you for customer services related matters; conduct research; and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

We collect certain information based on your navigation of our site through the use of log files, in order to better understand and serve our customers. This data allows us to improve and streamline your ability to navigate the site and develop featured programs and content that will be of interest to our members and site visitors. No Personal Information is collected during this process unless you explicitly provide it.

We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies (log files) to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate, including usage and volume statistics related to site visits, amount of time spent on the site, web browsers used by users, and geographic location of visitors, etc. This information is used to help us better understand the needs of our customers.

Personal Information can also be used to display targeted advertisements. Advertisement information is taken from data you explicitly provide on the NR web site, such as interests or of your group.

**How And With Whom Your Information Is Shared**

We do not rent, sell, share, or otherwise disclose Personal Information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We may use third party vendors and partners to assist us in providing our products or services and may transfer your Personal Information to such vendors who have entered into a contract with us that protects the confidentiality of your information and permits the vendor to use it only as necessary to fulfill its contract.

We may be required to disclose Personal Information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share Personal Information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law; to protect our interests or property; to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the NR service or using the NR name; or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

If you post Personal Information in areas of the site accessible to other users, it is important that you understand and be aware that such information can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and as a result could be used improperly to send you unsolicited messages. Please note, we are not responsible for the Personal Information you choose to submit in these forums or for others’ misuse of such information. Any misuse or improper collection of information provided on NR is a violation of the NR Terms of Use and should be reported to us as abuse. To help ensure your personal information is protected, we strongly recommend against posting your email address and other such Personal Information unless you are comfortable with the possibility of receiving unwanted contact.

Group Captains are allowed to email and add members to a NR group. NR will only use invitee email addresses to send invitations, updates, notices, reminders and messages by members of the NR group. Once the invitee receives the invite and registers with NR, that individual is considered a NR member and may receive the same type of communication from NR according to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.

If you have been invited to participate in a NR group, and you do not want to receive messages from the group captain or other members of the group, you may simply remove yourself from the group. To do this modify your user preferences in “my settings”.

**Cookies**

We set and access cookies on your computer as part of the service. A cookie is a small amount of data that our servers transfer to your browser and that only our servers can read. When you visit the site, the cookie captures specific session data to streamline your experience and, if you select to save your member name and password, we will save this information in a cookie so that you will not be required to sign in each time you visit the site. You may disable or delete cookies from within your Internet browser application by accessing the security or privacy settings, however we require you to have cookies enabled to access certain portions of the site.

A cookie file may also be placed on your hard drive by our third-party advertising companies. They automatically receive your IP Address when this happens. These companies may use also use other technologies such as JavaScript and “web beacons” (also known as “1×1 gifs”) to aggregate statistics about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about travel-related goods and services that you may be interested in. We do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your personal information stored on NRunless you choose to share it with them.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by us and doesn’t cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of our current or potential future advertisers.

**Links**

NR may contain links to other web sites either furnished by NR or created by your Group Captain. We unfortunately are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We strongly encourage you to be aware when you leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally Personal Information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us.

**Information Security**

We take appropriate physical and electronic measures to protect against unauthorized access to, alteration of, and disclosure of Personal Information.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Access to Personal Information is limited to employees who need to know that information in order to provide the Service and are bound by confidentiality agreements.

**Communication from NR**

We reserve the right to send NR group members certain communications relating to the NR service, such as service announcements, promotional or commercial communications, group updates, response to customer service inquiries and eNewsletters. You have the ability within “My Settings” to unsubscribe from most of these communications. However, certain communications, such as service announcements and administrative messages, are considered part of NR membership and you will not be able to opt out of receiving them.

We may offer our members and site visitors an opportunity to participate in surveys regarding their experience with our site. For our members, we may also send these surveys via e-mail. You are under no obligation to respond to any survey, and you may unsubscribe from receiving these e-mail surveys by following the unsubscribe instructions in any e-mail survey you.

**Changing or Removing Information**

We offer you the ability to access, review and change certain information via the My Settings (and Group Settings if you are the Captain) page. Upon your request, we will deactivate your account. Your account will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible. Please note that you should not expect that all of your Personal Information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your request, because we will retain some Personal Information to prevent possible fraud; collect any fees owed; assist users with any inquiries or investigations; enforce our Terms of Service; and comply with any legal requirements as permitted by law.

NR members are allowed to view, update, or delete any uploaded, inputted material they submitted. Where you make use of the communication features of NR to share information with other individuals on NR, however, (e.g., posting) you may not be able to remove such communications.

**Changes to the NR Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so our users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A user is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use users’ Personal Information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

**Questions**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of the Web site or the NR Group Pages, or your dealings with the Web site or the NR Groups, please don’t’ hesitate to contact us at nextround.net-at-gmail.com.
